<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<PartCollection>
    <Parts>
      <Part>
        <Name>Rodless Cylinder</Name>
        <PartNumber>OSP-P 32</PartNumber>
        <Info>
        The OSP-P rodless actuator in bore sizes Ø10, Ø16, Ø25, Ø32, Ø40, Ø50, Ø63 and Ø80mm is a combined linear actuator, guidance and control package with additional functions designed into modular system components. 
        Mounting rails on 3 sides of the cylinder enable modular components such as linear guides, brakes, valves, magnetic switches etc. 
        to be fitted to the cylinder itself solving many installation problems, especially where space is limited and forms an ideal basis for additional customer specific functions providing total installation flexibility. 
        Optimised cylinder profile for maximum stiffness and minimum weight, corrosion resistant steel outer sealing band, robust wiper system on the carrier for use in aggressive environments and a proven corrosion resistant steel inner band for optimum sealing. 
        OSP-P is available as standard temperature -10°C to +80°C with high and low temperature options and can be supplied with optional active or passive dynamic braking. 
        Long lifetime and service intervals up to 8,000km provide a unit ideally suited for point-to point operations, reciprocating movements and simple traverse / transfer applications.
        </Info>
      </Part>
      <Part>
        <Name>Pneumatic Cylinder</Name>
        <PartNumber>4MA</PartNumber>
        <Info>
        The 4MA series cylinder is a ruggedly constructed, highly configurable, all purpose design. 
        The aluminum body and machined aluminum end caps make the 4MA a light weight solution. 
        With 8 bore sizes, 20 NFPA mounting styles, and a variety of other options the 4MA is easily adaptable to practically any application. 
        Carboxilated nitrile seals, a urethane rod wiper, and piston wear band combine to offer low friction, leak free operation, and long service life. 
        To minimize downtime when maintenance is required, the externally removeable bronze gland enables servicing of the cylinder without disassembly of the body. 
        The 4MA series cylinder has a full range of features and options.
        </Info>
      </Part>
      <Part>
        <Name>Rotary Cylinder</Name>
        <PartNumber>MP5RS</PartNumber>
        <Info>
        The P5RS is a rotary table actuated using a twin rack and pinion design. 
        Stroke adjusters are standard and enable adjustment from 0 to 190 degrees of rotation. 
        The center shaft is hollow to allow piping, or wiring, to pass through to mounted accessories. 
        A magnetic piston is standard and shock absorbers are available.
        </Info>
      </Part>
      <Part>
        <Name>Guided Cylinder</Name>
        <PartNumber>P5T</PartNumber>
        <Info>
        The P5RS is a rotary table actuated using a twin rack and pinion design. 
        Stroke adjusters are standard and enable adjustment from 0 to 190 degrees of rotation. 
        The center shaft is hollow to allow piping, or wiring, to pass through to mounted accessories. 
        A magnetic piston is standard and shock absorbers are available.
        </Info>
      </Part>
      <Part>
        <Name></Name>
        <PartNumber></PartNumber>
        <Info></Info>
      </Part>
    </Parts>
</PartCollection>
